(Raj:)What should I do?
(Penny:)Okay, answer it.
Just be strong.
(Penny:)And if she starts to cry,
don't make any promises.
(Penny:)And most importantly, put it
on speaker so we can hear.
(Raj:)Hello?
(Emily(voice):)Hey, it's Emily.
(Emily(voice):)Is this a good time?
(Raj:)Yeah, yeah. Sure. What's up?
(Emily:)Was it okay I left that gift?
(Emily:)I'm really hoping
we can be friends.
(Raj:)Maybe, maybe.
(Emily:)Um, you think you'd want
to grab a cup of coffee?
(Raj:)Hello?
(Raj:)I'm sorry, I seem to be taking
an annoying amount of time
deciding how I feel about this!
(Emily:)I just...
I miss hanging out with you.
(Emily:)It's not like I lost a friend,
it's like I lost my best friend.
(choking up):
Is there any chance